{"Topic": "Sports", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "At which of the following tennis tournaments is the Musketeers' Trophy awarded to the winner of Singles title?", "op1": "Australian Open", "op2": "US Open", "op3": "French Open", "op4": "Wimbledon", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "What is the age from which certain category of sports persons winning gold medals at international levels are entitled to receive pension?", "op1": "30", "op2": "40", "op3": "50", "op4": "60", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Nine time Wimbledon Champion of Women\u2019s Singles Match in Tennis is -", "op1": "Mary Joe Fernandez", "op2": "Jana Novotna", "op3": "Iva Majoli", "op4": "Martina Navrotilova", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "The oldest Football Tournament in India is :", "op1": "Rovers Cup", "op2": "I. F. A. Shield", "op3": "Durand Cup", "op4": "Tata Cup", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "The modern game of polo originated in which of the following Indian states?", "op1": "Nagaland", "op2": "Manipur", "op3": "Mizoram", "op4": "Tripura", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which country has won the World Cup Football the maximum number of times?", "op1": "Germany", "op2": "Brazil", "op3": "England", "op4": "Argentina", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which Indian city is associated with the origin of badminton?", "op1": "Poona", "op2": "Shimla", "op3": "Mussoorie", "op4": "Ootacamund", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Manufacture of sports goods is an important industry in :", "op1": "Punjab", "op2": "Andhra Pradesh", "op3": "Karnataka", "op4": "Uttar Pradesh", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following international tennis tournaments is held on grass court?", "op1": "Australian Open", "op2": "Wimbledon", "op3": "French Open", "op4": "US Open", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Sambo, a form of martial arts is associated with which country?", "op1": "China", "op2": "Russia", "op3": "Japan", "op4": "Korea", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Who among the following was the first heavyweight boxer to go undefeated throughout his career?", "op1": "Rocky Marciano", "op2": "Lee Epperson", "op3": "Larry Holmes", "op4": "Michael Spinks", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Who was the first athlete to break the 10-second barrier in 100 metres sprint?", "op1": "Carl Lewis", "op2": "Calvin Smith", "op3": "Silvio Leonard", "op4": "Jim Hines"}, {"Question": "Who of the following was nicknamed the Flying Finn?", "op1": "Ville Ritola", "op2": "Paavo Nurmi", "op3": "Edvin Wide", "op4": "Joseph Guillemot", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Who of the following ran a mile in less than 4 minutes for the first time?", "op1": "John Landy", "op2": "Jesse Owens", "op3": "Roger Bannister", "op4": "Ben Johnson", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which is the reckoning year for beginning of Open Era tennis?", "op1": "1968", "op2": "1962", "op3": "1970", "op4": "1966", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Who of the following was the first gymnast to be awarded a perfect score of 10 in an Olympic event?", "op1": "Nadia Comaneci", "op2": "Lavinia Agache", "op3": "Emilia Eberle", "op4": "Daniela Silivas", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which of the following badminton tournaments does not have any prize money associated with it?", "op1": "Thomas Cup", "op2": "Uber Sup", "op3": "Sudirman Cup", "op4": "Malaysian Open", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "What is the official distance to be run in a marathon race?", "op1": "42.195 km", "op2": "41.295 km", "op3": "42.475 km", "op4": "41.745 km"}, {"Question": "A velodrome is an arena used for which of the following sports?", "op1": "Swimming", "op2": "Basketball", "op3": "Wrestling", "op4": "Cycling", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Who of the following holds the record in 100 m sprint for women made in 1988?", "op1": "Jackie Joyner Kersee", "op2": "Florence Griffith Joyner", "op3": "Evelyn Ashford", "op4": "Shelly-Ann Fraser-Pryce", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following is the oldest tennis tournaments?", "op1": "Australian Open", "op2": "French Open", "op3": "Davis Cup", "op4": "Wimbledon", "Answer": 4}]}